nerfplz.com 2019-06-30

# LoL Privacy Policy | NERFPLZ.LOL

###  Privacy Policy for nerfplz.com

The privacy of our visitors to nerfplz.com is important to us. 

At nerfplz.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit nerfplz.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

###  Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

We also use third party advertisements on nerfplz.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

###  Disclosure Regarding Google Display Advertising

We implement Google Analytics features that use Display Advertising information for Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising, to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, by going to the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

We, along with third-party vendors (including Google), use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookies) to report how your ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our website. You can read more about the cookies used by Google Analytics advertising features, by going to the [Google Analytics Privacy Policy page](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

###  Disclosure Regarding Amazon Associates

Nerfplz.com is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to amazon.com.

###  Disclosure Regarding Venatus

We use a third party provider, Venatus, to deliver targeted advertising and marketing to you. For information on how Venatus uses your data, please see Venatus’ privacy policy [here](https://www.venatusmedia.com/privacy/).
